ideas let's focus on some other stocks
where we are seeing earnings reaction
play out I say Lombard is in lower in
trade after reporting Q3 numbers survey
joins in with the fine print and what
missed the street expectation should be
hi thanks for that so I say Lombard is
in Focus today on back of their Q3
numbers the company has delivered a
healthy 17 premium growth led by health
and fire Insurance the pad growth came
in at 11 slightly lower than estimates
due to lower investment income and
that's what the state is concerned about
the most the combined ratio was broadly
stable at 104 the Roe came in at 14.3
percent similar to same time last year
the management has guided for continued
investments in retail Health business
lower combined ratio in fy24 an
improvement in Roe to High Teens going
forward most brokerages have cut Pat
estimates but still 18 or buy rating on
the stock Morgan Stanley has an
overweight rating with a Target price of
14.95. Jeffries and motilal both have a
buy rating with a Target price of 1620
and 1500 rupees per share potak has a
reduced rating with a Target price of
1225.
all right thanks a lot for that so
that's